Inspector: Ah, come in.
Barbara: Thank you.
Inspector: Can you confirm your name, please?
Barbara: Yes, I’m Barbara Travers.
Inspector: OK, Ms Travers, what did you do after dinner yesterday evening?
Barbara: After dinner? I played cards with Gordon, and then I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Barbara: It was about half past eleven. I remember, I looked at my watch
Inspector: Did you hear anything in your father’s room?
Barbara: No. I didn’t hear anything.
Inspector: Miss Travers, did you have any problems with your father?
Barbara: No, I didn’t have any problems with him at all. Daddy was a wonderful man, a wonderful father.
Sorry, Inspector.
Inspector: OK, Miss Travers. No more questions. Could you ask Mr Summers to come in, please?
Barbara: Of course.
Inspector: Mr Summers.
Gordon: Call me Gordon.
Inspector: Thank you, er…Gordon. What did you do after dinner?
Gordon: I played cards with Barbara. Then she went to bed.
Inspector: Did you go to bed then?
Gordon: No. I stayed in the living room and I had a glass of whisky. Then I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Gordon: I don’t remember exactly. I didn’t look at the time.
Inspector: Did you hear anything during the night?
Gordon: No, I didn’t. I was very tired. I slept very well.
Inspector: You and Mr Travers were business partners, weren’t you?
Gordon: Yes, that’s right.
Inspector: And it’s a very good business, I understand.
Gordon: Yes, Inspector, it is.
Inspector: And now it’s your business.
Gordon: Listen, Inspector, I did not kill Jeremy. He was my partner and he was my friend.
Inspector: Very well, Gordon. Could you ask Ms Pasquale to come in, please?
Gordon: Certainly.
Inspector: Ah, good morning Miss…
Claudia: Pasquale. Claudia Pasquale.
Inspector: Take a seat, Ms Pasquale.
Claudia: Thank you.
Inspector: So, Ms Pasquale, what did you do after dinner, yesterday evening?
Claudia: I went to my room and I had a bath and I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Claudia: About 11 o’clock.
Inspector: Did you hear anything?
Claudia: Yes. I heard somebody go into Jeremy’s room. It was about twelve o’clock.
Inspector: Who was it?
Claudia: It was Amanda, his wife.
Inspector: Are you sure? Did you see her?
Claudia: Well, no, I didn’t see her. But I’m sure it was Amanda.
Inspector: You were Mr Travers’s secretary, weren’t you Claudia?
Claudia: Yes, I was.
Inspector: Were you just his secretary?
Claudia: What do you mean?
Inspector: Were you in love with Mr Travers, Claudia?
Claudia: No, I wasn’t.
Inspector: The truth please, Claudia.
Claudia: Very well, Inspector. Yes, I was in love with him and he said that he was in love with me.
He said he wanted to leave his wife – Amanda – and marry me. I was stupid. I believed him.
But he didn’t leave her. He used me, Inspector! I was very angry with him.
Inspector: Did you kill him.
Claudia: No, Inspector. I loved Jeremy.